{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4344","name":"Sgt. Pepperoni's Pizzaria & Deli/GB","address":"4140 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Majestic Theatre Center Inc.","licenseNumber":"080863","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.06025,42.35105","geojson":{"id":"4344","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.060253586,42.351053272]},"properties":{"name":"Sgt. Pepperoni's Pizzaria & Deli/GB","owner":"Majestic Theatre Center Inc.","address":"4140 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"080863","establishmentid":"4344","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"5/13/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1098","name":"Union Street Detroit","address":"4145 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5059","name":"Popolux","address":"4120 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"589","name":"Majestic Cafe/The Majestic Theater","address":"4120 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4345","name":"The Magic Stick/Alley Deck","address":"4120 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4818","name":"Midtown Zef's","address":"4160 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51623110","name":"Midtown Zef's","address":"4160 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4408","name":"The Great Lakes Coffee Roasting Co.","address":"3965 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","address":"4206 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4956","name":"Falafill","address":"4206 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5202","name":"Rock City Eatery","address":"4216 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"51009","inspectionDate":"2020-03-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"7-202.12","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS shall be:    \r\n(A) Used according to:      \r\n(1) LAW and this Code,   \r\n(2) Manufacturer's use directions included in labeling, and, for a pesticide, manufacturer's label instructions that state that use is allowed in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, (P)   \r\n(3) The conditions of certification, if certification is required, for use of the pest control materials, (P) and   \r\n(4) Additional conditions that may be established by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY; and\r\n(B) Applied so that:      \r\n(1) A HAZARD to EMPLOYEES or other PERSONS is not constituted, (P) and   \r\n(2) Contamination including toxic residues due to drip, drain, fog, splash or spray on FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES is prevented, and for a RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE, this is achieved by: (P)      \r\n(a) Removing the items, (P)   \r\n(b) Covering the items with impermeable covers, (P) or   \r\n(c) Taking other appropriate preventive actions, (P) and   \r\n(d) Cleaning and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS after the application. (P)  \r\n(C) A RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE shall be applied only by an applicator certified as defined in 7 USC 136 Definitions, (e) Certified Applicator, of the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act, or a PERSON under the direct supervision of a certified applicator. (Pf)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"restricted use","problemDescription":"Not used according to manufacturer's label instructions","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Below the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Above the Pizza station","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Food contact surfaces","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"49234","inspectionDate":"2019-09-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"cockroaches","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"beverage dispensing nozzles","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Pop gun holsters","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45364","inspectionDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (pizza-prep)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-501.18","violationDescription":"The wash, rinse, and SANITIZE solutions shall be maintained clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing solutions","subItem":"sanitizing","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Pop gun holsters","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (undercounter)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43097","inspectionDate":"2018-08-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Food contact surfaces","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Lack of DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"ice bin(s) in ice machine","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT STOREROOM","subLocation":"Ice machine","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without packaging/wrapping","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT STOREROOM","subLocation":"Single service items","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide packaging/wrapping."}]},{"inspectionid":"41447","inspectionDate":"2018-02-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Fail to require employees to report illness as rule requires","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-02-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Require reporting as stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Food contact surfaces","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-02-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"ice bin(s) in ice machine","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT STOREROOM","subLocation":"Ice machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without packaging/wrapping","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT STOREROOM","subLocation":"Single service items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide packaging/wrapping."}]},{"inspectionid":"39476","inspectionDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Lack of DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Pop gun holsters","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Cooler(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37561","inspectionDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"UNAPPROVED Sanitizer","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Cooler (beer)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"beverage dispensing nozzles","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Beverage gun nozzle(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4344"}}